

1401-4132 Halifax Street, Burnaby, BC, V5C 6V1, Canada

□ (+1) 250-715-6128 | ■ mikeachester@gmail.com | ♠ chester.io | • mchestr | • mchestr

Summary_

Senior full stack developer with 7+ years of Industry experience. My practical experience includes infrastructure automation, backend software development, application security, support, testing, and people management. I strive to keep up to date with the latest technologies and best practises and try to incorporate them wherever feasible.

Experience _____

Idemia Vancouver BC, Canada

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Feb. 2018 - Present

- Project lead and backend Python developer working on core ESIM orchestration product
- · Designed, implemented, and tested the separation of the e-commerce platform from the core product
- · Provide mentorship and feedback for team members on design and implementation of customer projects within product
- Developed scripts and tooling to assist in managing and debugging orchestration product
- Technologies: Python(Flask), Go, Clojure, PostgreSQL, RabbitMQ, Kafka, Salt Stack, AWS

CA Technologies Vancouver BC, Canada

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Aug. 2016 - Feb. 2018

- Full stack Java developer on the API Management Portal product
- Mentored employees on Python scripting and git best practices
- Developed Python scripts to help onboard new and existing customers
- · Leader for an internal API first group, to help guide teams to develop APIs following best practises
- Technologies: Java(Spring Boot), Python, Docker, Kubernetes, PostgreSQL, RabbitMQ, OpenShift, TeamCity

Siaras

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Burnaby BC, Canada

May 2014 - Aug. 2016

- Core Python developer working on the Siaras cloudScape/cloudBurst product
- Involved in designing, documenting, implementing, and testing many areas of cloudScape
- Developed solutions for abstracting different cloud technologies into a single common OpenStack API layer
- Helped develop creative WAN solutions using a variety of technologies such as GRE, VPN, and L2 Gateway
- Developed end-to-end tests which integrate into our CI infrastructure
- Technologies: Python, MongoDB, OpenStack

Education _____

University of Victoria BC, Canada

BACHELORS OF ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Sept. 2009 - May 2014

Publications and Awards

Dynamic web cache publishing for IaaS clouds using Shoal, Ian Gable, Michael Chester, Patrick

2013 Armstrong, Frank Berghaus, Andre Charbonneau, Colin Leavett-Brown, Michael Paterson, Robert Prior, Randall Sobie and Ryan Taylor

arXiv: 1311.0058

2013 Undergraduate Student Research Award, NSERC

References

Available Upon Request

JANUARY 9, 2020 MIKE CHESTER · RÉSUMÉ 1